[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":112385,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":1401039,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure  that whe n we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":11640,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":1412683,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":17591,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":1430277,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":3228,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":1433509,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":5549,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":1439060,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1805,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":1440869,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to  get your  result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":5053,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":1445924,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1645,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":1447572,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":15310,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":1462884,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub> 6</sub>  1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1551,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":1464438,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":5708,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":1470149,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1701,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":1471852,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you  start w ith the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4126,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":1475980,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1926,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":1477909,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":[" 4"],"rt":3773,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":1481684,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1424,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":1483109,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3477,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":1486588,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1540,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":1488132,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4110,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":1492244,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1550,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":1493796,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the  sum is  6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":5551,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":1499349,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":5804,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":1505156,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":19586,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":1524749,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":69007,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":1593757,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":7468,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":1601229,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1870,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":1603101,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":5118,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":1608221,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1894,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":1610116,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7 -0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["2","3"],"rt":5319,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":1615437,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1404,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":1616844,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":4119,"trial_type":"que stion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":1620965,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1453,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":1622420,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3742,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":1626164,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":26166,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":1652332,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":75935,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":1728269,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a < i>genera tor</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":85678,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":1813949,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":34764,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":1848717,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":17924,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":1866644,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4614,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":1871260,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":23118,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":1894380,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10- 0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":38901,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":1933285,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":21531,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":1954820,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["No","Yes"],"rt":25574,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":1980396,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":8157,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":1988556,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure yo u unders tand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":95054,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":2083612,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":6917,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":2090532,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1950,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":2092484,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":5478,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":2097964,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":12470,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":2110436,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":6740,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":2117180,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":11173,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":2128356,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4574,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":2132932,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"4*1=5 5 is less than 9 so 5 is the answer","response_history":["4*1=5 5 is less than 9 so 5 is the answer"],"rt":39942,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":2172876,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"8+4=12 12-9=3 3 is the answer because you have to subtract 9 from answers that are 9 or greater","response_history":["8+4=12 12+","8+4=12 12-9=3 3 is the naswer becasue you have to substract 9 from answers that are 9 or greater","8+4=12 12-9=3 3 is the answer because you have to subtr act 9 fr om answers that are 9 or greater"],"rt":66413,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":2239292,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0 is the identity, what two inverse numbers added together, will get to the identity","response_history":["0 is the identity, what two numbers added together, will ","0 is the identity, what two inumbers added together, will ","0 is the identity, what two innumbers added together, will ","0 is the identity, what two invnumbers added together, will ","0 is the identity, what two invernumbers added together, will ","0 is the identity, what two inversnumbers added together, will ","0 is the identity, what two inversenumbers added together, will ","0 is the identity, what two inverse numbers added together, will get to the identity"],"rt":135190,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":2374484,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":10181,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":2384667,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":4863,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":2389531,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","response_history":["9"],"rt":6057,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":2395589,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3+6=9 9-9=0 To find the inverse I want to get to zero ","response_history":["3+6=9 9-9=0 To find the inverse I want to get to zero "],"rt":40989,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":2436580,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes you can make the numbers 0-9 with a 2","response_history":["yes yi","yes you can make the numbers 0-9 with a 2"],"rt":118189,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":2554771,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your  answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no way to get to some numbers ","response_history":["no way to get to some numbers "],"rt":87799,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":2642571,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no I cant get to all of the numbers with 5 and -9","response_history":["no I cant get to all of the ni","no I cant get to all of the numbers with 5 and -9"],"rt":102042,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":2744614,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6 no i still can't get to all the numbers wit h 6 and  -9 ","response_history":["6 no i still can't get to all the numbers with 6 and -9 "],"rt":32572,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":2777187,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":23103,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":2800291,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 + n _ = 0","response_history":["1 -","1 6 ","1 6","1 + n _ = 0"],"rt":40911,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":2841203,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x + n _ = 0 what number added to x minus  n equals zero ","response_history":["x + n _ = 0 what number added to x minus  n equals zero "],"rt":55039,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":2896243,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I see the pattern when I add each number to 1 through 9 and ten subtract 9 if needed to get the answers 0 - 9 ","response_history":["I see the pattern when I add each number to 1 throug h 9 and  ten sun","I see the pattern when I add each number to 1 through 9 and ten subtract 9 if needed to get the answers 0 - 9 "],"rt":52839,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2949083,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":31031,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2980115,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":5527,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2985643,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True  or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":12679,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2998323,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"you need to be able to subtract n from the answers greater than n to get to 0 through n for answers","response_history":["you need to be able to subtract n fro mm","you need to be able to subtract n fro m t","you need to be able to subtract n fro m ","you need to be able to subtract n fro m","you need to be able to subtract n fro ","you need  to be a ble to subtract n fro","you need to be able to subtract n from the answers greater than n to get tp","you need to be able to subtract n from the answers greater than n to get to 0- n","you need to be able to subtract n from the answers greater than n to get to 0- ","you need to be able to subtract n from the answers greater than n to get to 0-","you need to be able to subtract n from the answers greater than n to get to 0 through n for answers"],"rt":76255,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":3074579,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":16414,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":3090995,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"some answers less than n wont use n so the rule won't always apply ","response_history":["some answers less than n wont use n so they ","some answers less than n wont use n so they","some answers less than n wont use n so the rule won't alway apply ","some answers less than n wont use n so the rule won't always apply "],"rt":45143,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":3136139,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":5719,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":3141859,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":2231,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":3144091,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"38","response_history":["38"],"rt":3335,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":3147427,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate,  M.D., et c."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":3863,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":3151291,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"basic math, I hope I understood this OK ","response_history":["basic math, i hope i i","basic math, i hope i understood this OK ","basic math, i hope  understood this OK ","basic math, i hope I understood this OK ","basic math,  hope I understood this OK ","basic math, I hope I understood this OK "],"rt":26550,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":3177843,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":5407,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":3183251,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3671,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":3186923,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"D o you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4543,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":3191467,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":5495,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":3196963,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":3007,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":3199971,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":3223,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":3203195,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":6711,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":3209907,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes, I worked some on scratch paper ","response_history":["yesm","yes, i worked some on scr ac","yes , i worked some on scratch paper ","yes,  worked some on scratch paper ","yes, I worked some on scratch paper "],"rt":21639,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":3231547,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"wow, interesting, thank you","response_history":["wow, interesting, thank you"],"rt":9991,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":3241539,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]